One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
It's not like we've seen
the end of the world with our own eyes.
That's why we gotta cast off - together, we can!
Sailing from sea to sea,
saying it's nothing but a fairy tale.
Truth is stranger than fiction, isn't it?
Don't pretend you can't see it.
Common sense is only what the majority says it is!
It's not like we've seen
the end of the world with our own eyes.
So let's go, Captain I'll-Do-It-My-Way!
Whaddya mean, "no can do"?
We haven't even started yet!
I wanna know it all! Now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can! This moment...
We can! I can! With this feeling of freedom...
Now... Now, oh yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
Master Nekomamushi!
He's a wonderful person!
I like him so much, so I wrote a song about him.
Let's Go See Master Nekomamushi
Let's go and meet Master Nekomamushi
Nami. I don't see Sanji or Cedar.
Don't tell me they were taken away...
No, he went willingly.
What?
Wanda! Carrot!
They-gara want you to forget about it.
You must understand.
We'll take care of Pekoms too.
Don't give the daytime people unnecessary anxiety.
Thank you, Master.
You-gara guys showed concern for our broken-hearted citizens.
We should thank you.
There's silver vine!
Master Nekomamushi gets lonely easily
When I think of him like that it makes my heart twinge
When he is bathed in the moonlight his face looks innocent
He gazes up at it with his sparkling eyes
But he tries to act tough under the sun
He does his best and lives his life on his own
I like that song.
Is Master Nekomamushi really like that?
Not at all.
He's not?!
It's just a song inspired by him.
Then, "gotta go see a woman" means...
...he's gonna get married?
That's not necessarily the case but...
...it seemed like he was determined.
Oh, maybe he'll return with his wife.
What?!
In that case, we'll get a new member!
Luffy-san.
The bride is the Emperor's daughter.
That means we'll become Big Mom's subordinates.
No!
Of course, Sanji-san doesn't want that either.
He refused it firmly right there.
But that troubles me.
Considering who he is dealing with this time,
if he couldn't avoid the marriage,
what do you think he would do?
Well, he would...
Yeah, he's the kind of guy who'll try not to cause us any trouble...
So he'd try to separate himself from us!
You mean Sanji will quit this group?!
That's even more unacceptable!
When he tossed us out, he could've gotten away too.
When he wrote the note, I think he'd already made up his mind to go by himself.
Big Mom's daughter, huh?
He got a pretty troublesome offer of marriage.
And did you say Vinsmoke?
I guess that family is the key.
It could be Sanji's father or mother or brother...
They once lived in the North Blue and then moved to the East Blue and now, they're in the New World.
Unbelievable!
Vinsmoke...
I think I've heard of them before...
We're sorry.
I wish we could've stopped him at least until you guys arrived...
Sanji wouldn't let you stop him.
It's not your fault, guys.
But, Robin,
what if we never get to see him again?!
Nothing wrong with that.
Huh?!
I mean, if he was leaving for good,
he should've said
"Thank you for everything."
And "I'm sorry for causing so much trouble."
No, that's not the point!
Think about it.
We're on an unstoppable train now.
Remember what Caesar said?
The biggest customer of SMILEs,
the artificial Devil Fruits, is Kaidou.
We pissed Doflamingo off
by destroying the lab on Punk Hazard,
we destroyed the SMILE factory in Dressrosa,
and the man who's gonna go nuts next is...
...Emperor Kaidou!
He's not some distant threat anymore.
We've already had a fight with his subordinates,
the Beast Pirates.
Jack who ruined this country, and others will
come after us in a matter of time!
We're allying with Tra-guy for upcoming battles.
I don't know why but it seems like Kin'emon and the others are targeted by Kaidou too.
We'll face Emperor Kaidou very soon!
How stupid can he be to get involved with another Emperor, Big Mom, now?!
That twirly-eyebrowed fool!
Don't say it like that!
You boorish son of a gun!
Those things are unrelated!
First of all, how could he get wrapped up in
such a thing as marriage?! It's such a small deal!
What did you say?!
Both of you! Don't get so heated up!
It is a big deal!
You can't say someone else's problem is big or small!
What?!
All right!
We don't know what's on his mind
so let's go ask him!
Huh?
What?!
Hey! Forget it, Luffy!
Don't tell me we're gonna head for Big Mom!
I guess so.
Did you forget that you picked a fight with her?!
Without a strategy or reinforcements,
we'll just get beaten and that'll be it!
She's an Emperor.
Luffy! Don't forget. She's on a totally different level than any of our past enemies.
Then, we'll go quietly.
How do we find them?!
Well, there is a way to go after them but...
He's right.
Sanji-san has gone because of the Big Mom Pirates...
But they left something big behind instead.
If that person is awake now,
there should be something he can tell us.
Let's just keep going.
This place has been totally wrecked.
Whale Forest
Dwelling of the Guardians
The Whale Tree looks even bigger up close!
Hey, guys!
It's the Straw Hats!
Chopper is here!
Garchu!
The Minks are recovering fast, aren't they?
You're right.
Straw Hat Luffy!
It's us!
Sorry for what we did in the forest.
Doesn't matter who it is,
we can't let any invader get by!
Oh, it's you guys!
Well, never mind!
Um, where's Nekomamushi?
I'm glad to see you!
Our saviors and their friends!
Let me say it once again.
Thank you!
Who is this?!
Captain of the Whale Forest Guardians
(Jaguar Mink)
Treetop Pedro
Sorry for my subordinates' action in the forest.
They were too wary of invaders.
Were you there?
Yes, I was up in a tree.
Bepo and the others are waiting for you-gara guys back there.
We can see them later.
We wanna see Master Nekomamushi and Pekomamushi the lion first.
Garchu!
If you're talking about Pekoms, he's up now.
He's in the building at the back.
We kept the whole incident secret from everybody.
Sanji is a nice guy.
I hope we can help you in some way.
Luffy! I'm worried about Nakomamushi; not just about his condition,
so I'll go see him first!
Okay!
Then, let me lead the way, Dr. Chopper.
Hey, Chopper! Why are you frozen?
I-I-I'm not frozen.
You're acting strange.
It's this way.
O-Okay!
Master Nekomamushi is taking a bath now.
A bath?!
SAKE
PROTECT
Lasagna!
It's good-meow! Yeah!
Hey, Nekomamushi!
You shouldn't take a bath!
Your wound is gonna reopen!
And you should eat light meals!
Why are you using your left hand?!
Are you listening to me?!
Oh, Chopper!
No problem. No problem!
I'm a freedom-loving man!
You have to listen to your doctor!
He's larger than I expected.
I'm sorry but even if it's a doctor's instruction...
Whoops...
I don't care!
I still can't get used to not having a left hand!
I can't even clap my hands like this!
So you-gara people are the Straw Hats!
You saved me!
Thank you!
I'll repay my debt to you someday!
I may not look it but
I have a strong sense of obligation and compassion!
Oh, a ball.
Yeah! A ball!
I told you to rest!
See! The wound reopened!
Listen, I...
I got into bed because I wanted to.
Uh-huh, uh-huh, okay.
Whatever the case, just stay still!
I'm gonna give you a shot.
Hey, you-gara!
Show me that foxtail right there.
Like this?
Chopper!
Hurry up while I'm distracted and enjoying myself!
I told you to stay still!
Are you afraid of shots?!
Even looking like that?!
It's completely cured now.
There's no wonder drug like that so keep quiet!
Don't hit an injured person.
Boy, he's so funny!
I love him!
I can't believe you survived!
I blocked about half of the attack
with my ability! Grr!
Bege, that bastard!
I'm sorry.
They must've taken Black-Leg with them.
He can't get away from the wedding now!
Yeah, about that, Pekomamushi...
Who arranged the marriage?
Well, of course, our Mama and the father of the Vinsmoke Family!
Sanji-kun's father?!
What kind of person is he?!
He's quite infamous in the underworld.
Have you ever heard the name, Germa 66?
Also known as the Warmongers.
What are you talking about?!
That's a mythical evil army!
How ridiculous!
No, it's an actual organization.
The Vinsmoke Family is at the top of it!
And their boss is Black-Leg's father!
Believe this if nothing else.
I didn't mean to hide anything from my friends.
The Vinsmoke Family is, well, to put it simply...
A family of assassins!
Sanji-kun is from a family of assassins?!
I don't know what you're talking about and I don't care!
Grr! I'm sure you don't!
What we wanna know is
whether he'll come back or not!
He can get married if he wants!
But we don't wanna become Big Mom's subordinates because of it!
So if they get married,
you guys become my subordinates!
Ouch!
Pekoms, are you okay?
Luffy, you're funny!
Watch what you say, you brat!
Or I'll destroy you!
Grr!
I owe you guys but don't push your luck!
Mama is one of the Four Emperors of the sea!
Uh-huh.
This is bad for my wound.
You have pretty eyes.
Shut up!
Well, either way,
he can't escape the marriage.
Why?!
Just like Black-Leg has gone to attend it,
no one can turn down an invitation
to Mama's tea party on any account.
If anybody turns it down, they'll get themselves quite a shocking present.
Because they put Mama to shame.
It's not the kind of present you want.
Inside they would receive the decapitated head of a person who was close to them!
It could be a head of someone
from the Straw Hats...
...or someone from the restaurant
in the East Blue.
Oh, it could be someone from the Kamabakka Kingdom.
Hey!
How do you guys know about all those things?!
That's what power can do, Straw Hat!
What he was told at that
time must have been...
When someone as powerful as that makes a threat, it's definitely not idle.
Who can fight it?
That's how powerful the Four Emperors are!
There's really nothing you can do about it!
That's why Sanji-kun had no choice but to go!
There's one other thing.
Let me ease your worry, my saviors.
You guys will not become
her subordinates. Grr!
It's a political marriage.
Mama always forms a connection with those who'll become her subordinates.
So this marriage is a ritual
to form a connection between the Vinsmoke Family and the Charlotte Family.
It's got nothing to do with you guys.
Do you want me to break it down for you more?
From the moment they get married,
Black-Leg Sanji will no longer
be part of your crew!
What?!
That's totally unacceptable!
Sanji's my friend!
But he's Vinsmoke's son first!
Don't get mad at me! Grr!
I know Sanji will refuse such a marriage!
In the face of Mama and the vicious Vinsmoke Family?
Well, I wonder if he can manage to stay alive after he refuses.
What do you mean?!
Hey, Pekomamushi!
What are you gonna do now?!
I'll go back to Mama after I get well.
That bastard Bege thinks he killed me!
But he can't get away with it!
Then, take me with you!
Luffy!
Nami, I'm gonna go by myself.
What?
Like Robin and the others said, if we go together, it'd seem like we want a war.
We don't have time for that.
I'll go by myself!
If I go with him, maybe I can sneak into the tea party and ruin the wedding.
Screw you!
Are you asking me to harbor an enemy?!
Oh, sounds like fun!
Carrot, this is serious!
Okay, it's a deal!
H-Hey!
Ouch!
I'll get Chopper! Get well already!
Don't just decide that!
Ow, ow... Hey!
Wait, Straw Hat!
Zoro, you're here!
Did you hear all that?!
Just barely.
You're worried about Sanji, aren't you?
I'll kick you, fool!
I told you to forget about that idiot!
Hey!
Luffy! Zoro! How's Pekoms doing?!
Oh, Chopper!
He's crying from pain and banging his head against a wall and yelling!
Cure him now!
Those are crazy symptoms!
I'll check him right away!
Garchu! Baron Corpe!
Oh! You-gara are Straw Hat Luffy, aren't you?!
I couldn't wait to meet you!
What?! Why did you follow us?! Get rest!
I just got better!
No, you didn't!
He's huge! Is that Nekomamushi?!
He's a cat monster!
A Garchu of thanks!
Nekomamushi is spouting blood!
Hey, what are you doing, cat monster!?
Stay with me! Nekomamushi!
What's going on?
I'm out of blood!
Bring me some blood quick!
Okay, Dr. Chopper.
Th-Th-Th-Thank...
What's wrong, Chopper?!
Cat monster, stand up! I'll cut you up!
Whoa-whoa, he's injured.
Oh, Tra-guy!
Oh! Are they your friends?!
Yeah, I came to introduce them to you.
They're my crew; 20 in total!
It's nice to make your acquaintance! Straw Hat!
Heart Pirates
Yeah!
We need to talk.
What?! Is that it?!
Heartless! Heartless!
Heartless! Heartless! Heartless! Heartless! Heartless!
We feel slighted, Captain!
We're just allies.
We don't necessarily have to get friendly.
Help me...
What?! Black-Foot-ya went to Big Mom?!
Uh-huh.
How in the world could that happen?!
Don't worry!
I'm gonna go take him back!
So could you wait to fight
Kaidou a little bit?!
That's not my call!
It's only a matter of time
before Kaidou comes after us!
I thought we could hide ourselves here in Zou for a while but they know where it is.
Even if their target is us next, what do you think will happen to this country if it's attacked again?!
How kind of you!
Since when were they there?!
Garchu!
You-gara guys, are you really pirates?!
Thank you for caring about us
on top of saving us!
Thank you! Garchu!
Oh, Pekoms, are you hurt?
Yeah...
Well, who cares!
Okay, let's have a banquet!
Bring drinks and food!
Why, Nekomamushi?!
I'm in!
No you're not!
Seems like Luffy-san and the others are completely forgetting about it.
But we mature adults must get our act together.
That's right.
This country doesn't want them.
Yeah! Under no circumstances should a samurai enter!
After all, Raizo-san, the person Kin'emon-san and
Kanjurou-san are looking for, isn't here so there's no point to enter.
In addition, because of that,
the millennium-old city was ruined!
Bring Raizo here!
Where's the warrior from the Land of Wano?
They call us saviors and thank us.
So we absolutely can't tell them
that we actually have some samurai friends.
If they find out that Kin'emon and the others were going to use this island as their rendezvous point...
Even the cheerful Minks would be pissed off.
I don't wanna fight them
after we got to know each other!
Let's keep guard all night long
to prevent Kin'emon and Kanjurou from entering.
The next morning
Well... Well, well, well,
it's still dark so it's before dawn.
We made it!
That's right! We finally made it!
Oh boy, it was a disaster,
but all's well that ends well.
I'm sure Luffy-dono and everybody are worried about us.
I feel bad.
Yes, they must've been waiting for us!
Well done, Torasaburo.
Tora-?!
Oh, I didn't know this animal was a tiger!
Note: tora = tiger
Alright, that's enough.
Revert to a painting!
But monkey fellow,
you didn't tell us anything after all.
I just wanna know
if a warrior named Raizo is...
I-I don't know anything-saru!
What's the matter? You look pale...
Oh, hey, wait! Where are you going?!
We can't look for Raizo on our own!
Wait, monkey fellow!
We need you to take us around!
Oh no-saru! Samurai are here-saru!
I gotta let them know as soon as possible!
Samurai are here-saru!